http://www.amhfcu.org/terms-of-use

Skip to main content
Download Our Mobile App!
Deposit checks, pay bills, manage your accounts, view transaction history and more - right from your phone!
Member Notice
To protect our members, branch access has temporarily changed. Transactions are available at drive-thru locations and lobby services are available by appointment. Click here to learn more about branch accessibility and staying connected.
Search
Login
Routing Number: 236082944
Personal
Checking
Online & Mobile Access
Checking Accounts
Independence Debit Card
Terms of Use
THESE TERMS OF USE GOVERN THE ACCESS AND USE OF OUR WEBSITE AND SHOULD BE CAREFULLY READ. BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE, THE USER ACCEPTS AND AGREES TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS OF USE AS THEY MAY FROM TIME TO TIME BE MODIFIED BY AMERICAN HERITAGE CREDIT UNION AND ITS AFFILIATES (COLLECTIVELY, “AMERICAN HERITAGE”) WITHOUT NOTICE.Use of WebsiteOur website contains information, names, images, pictures, logos, icons, documents and other material (the "Contents") for the use and information of American Heritage members and other visitors to our website. The Contents may not be copied (other than a copy for personal use), modified, distributed, transmitted, displayed, performed, reproduced, transferred, resold or republished without the prior written consent of AMERICAN HERITAGE, which it may withhold in its sole discretion.ModificationsAMERICAN HERITAGE may at any time make modifications, changes, and alterations to the contents of this website, including these Terms of Use, without prior notice. Users are responsible for regularly reviewing these Terms of Use. Your continued use of this website following any modifications, changes or alterations shall constitute your acceptance of each such modification, change or alteration.
Transmissions to and from this WebsiteExcept when utilizing the forms within our website or when expressly indicated as being secure, transmissions to and from this website or directed to AMERICAN HERITAGE, including emails, are not sent in a secure form and can be intercepted by third parties and may not be immediately received by the appropriate business unit at AMERICAN HERITAGE. Please do not use email other than the forms within our website to send us communications that contain confidential information, which we require to be in writing, or which need our immediate attention. Please contact us at 215-969-0777, visit an AMERICAN HERITAGE branch, or visit us at 2060 Red Lion Rd., Philadelphia, PA 19115 to communicate confidential information. Any transmission to this website, including emails, shall be deemed and remain the property of AMERICAN HERITAGE. AMERICAN HERITAGE may use and provide information contained in any such transmission (including any ideas, concepts, know-how or other intellectual property) to any of its affiliates for any purpose whatsoever and as deemed appropriate by AMERICAN HERITAGE. Users should be aware that linked sites (see "Linked Sites", below) may utilize privacy policies which differ from ours. AMERICAN HERITAGE is not responsible for such policies and expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such policies. Be aware of the unsecure nature of emails with any link to an email address.CookiesCookies are small strings of text that a website can send to your computer. A cookie cannot retrieve any data from your hard drive, pass on computer viruses or capture personal information such as your email address. Currently, websites use cookies to enhance the user's visit; in general, cookies can securely store a user's ID and password, personalize home pages, identify which parts of a site have been visited or keep track of selections in a "shopping cart.” If you become a registered user with a designated user ID and password, we use cookies so that we can provide customized information that we believe will be of value to you based on preferences indicated, other information we have about you as an AMERICAN HERITAGE member, as well as information available from external sources such as the census bureau. If you are a registered user and are visiting the site to, for example, perform banking transactions, you must accept the website's cookies as they are essential for site administration and security.Copyrights and Other Intellectual PropertyExcept where otherwise expressly noted or as noted below, all contents of this website, including the graphics, icons and overall appearance of the website, are the sole and exclusive property of American Heritage Bancorp Inc. and/or its subsidiaries or affiliates. The posting of the contents of this website neither constitutes a waiver of any of AMERICAN HERITAGE's proprietary rights or any other party's proprietary rights, including but not limited to, copyrights, trademarks, service marks, patents and other intellectual property, nor a transfer by implication, estoppel or otherwise of any such rights or of any license to the website user or to any third party. Contents of this website are protected by United States and international copyright laws, both as individual works and as a collection and by United States and international trademark laws. You agree not to delete any copyright, trademark or similar notice from any contents that you obtain from the website. The display of trademarks within this website does not grant you a license of any kind. Any downloading of material contained in the site, or of any site linked to the site, may be a violation of federal trademark and copyright laws. Any downloading of contents of this website or any website linked to this website may be a violation of federal and other trademark laws and federal copyright laws.Linked SitesWe allow our website users to directly access non-AMERICAN HERITAGE websites and content by providing links users to third-party sites, and by bringing third-party content into our site via "inverse" hyperlinks and framing technology (a "linked site"). We provide these links solely as convenient pointers to information on topics that may be useful to users of our website and we have no control over the content on such non-AMERICAN HERITAGE websites. Should you choose to visit, via our link, a non-AMERICAN HERITAGE website, AMERICAN HERITAGE makes no warranties, either express or implied, concerning the content of such site, including the accuracy, completeness, reliability or suitability thereof for any particular purpose, nor does AMERICAN HERITAGE warrant that such site or content is free from any claims of copyright, trademark or other infringement of the rights of third parties or that such site or content is devoid of viruses or other contamination. AMERICAN HERITAGE urges users to understand these risks before using, relying upon or retrieving information from a linked site. Links to non-AMERICAN HERITAGE sites do not imply any endorsement of or responsibility for the opinions, ideas, products, information or services offered at such sites, or any representation regarding the content at such sites. Linked sites may have privacy policies that differ from ours. Click on Electronic Privacy Policy to view our current electronic privacy policy. The providers of linked sites may not be bound by federal regulation, as AMERICAN HERITAGE is, to disclose your personal information only in compliance with such regulations. Be aware of the unsecure nature of emails with any link to an email address.No WarrantiesAlthough AMERICAN HERITAGE attempts to ensure that the Contents provided or otherwise displayed on our website are accurate, we make no representation, endorsement or warranty that the Contents are accurate or suitable for your particular purpose. THE WEBSITE AND ITS CONTENTS ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS. USE OF THE WEBSITE AND ITS CONTENTS IS AT THE USER'S SOLE RISK. THE WEBSITE AND ITS CONTENTS ARE PROVIDED WITHOUT ANY REPRESENTATIONS, ENDORSEMENTS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ANY WARRANTIES OF TITLE OR ACCURACY AND ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT, WITH THE SOLE EXCEPTION OF WARRANTIES (IF ANY) WHICH CANNOT BE EXPRESSLY EXCLUDED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW.Limitation of LiabilityIN NO EVENT WILL AMERICAN HERITAGE OR ITS SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, REPRESENTATIVES, CONTRACTORS, OR THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS OR EMPLOYEES BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, WHETHER UNDER A CONTRACT, TORT OR ANY OTHER THEORY OF LIABILITY, ARISING IN CONNECTION WITH ANY PARTY'S USE OF OUR WEBSITE OR A LINKED SITE, ANY FAILURE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY, COMPUTER VIRUS, LINE SYSTEM FAILURE OR LOSS OF DATA; ANY LOSS OF USE RELATED TO OUR WEBSITE OR A LINKED SITE; ANY WEBSITE OPERATED BY ANY THIRD PARTY; OR ANY CONTENTS OF THIS WEBSITE OR ANY LINKED SITE, EVEN IF AMERICAN HERITAGE IS AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. Available Only Where Permitted by LawThe products and services of AMERICAN HERITAGE are available only in the United States and other countries where permitted by law, to qualified members.Governing LawThese Terms of use shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the law of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, without regard to the conflict of laws thereof, and to the laws of the United States.VenueDisputes arising from the use of this website shall be exclusively subject to the jurisdiction of any federal or state court for the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania.SeverabilityIf a court of competent jurisdiction determines that a portion of our Terms of Use is unenforceable, such portion shall be modified solely to the extent necessary to cause such portion to be enforceable and these Terms of Use as so modified shall otherwise remain in full force and effect.WaiverNo waiver by AMERICAN HERITAGE of any right under or term or provision of these Terms of Use will be deemed a waiver of any other right, term, or provision of these Terms of Use at that time or a waiver of that or any other right, term, or provision of these Terms of Use at any other time.AccessibilityWe are committed to making our content accessible to individuals with disabilities and are continually working to increase accessibility and usability. We continually monitor and test our website in order for it to meet the accessibility requirements as defined by World Wide Web Consortium's Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG 2.0AA).AMERICAN HERITAGE has incorporated design best practices into its website so that the pages are accessible to people with physical and visual impairments, including those who need screen readers, those who are color blind and those who cannot use a mouse.Currently, our website may not meet all the WCAG 2.0AA standards despite our best efforts. Some documents on the AMERICAN HERITAGE website are in portable document format (PDF). For the best experience viewing these files, please download the latest version of Adobe Acrobat Reader, which is available for free at the Adobe website. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) American Heritage Credit Union (American Heritage) provides Youth and Learning sections of its website for the convenience and education of youth members and their parent(s)/guardian(s). In partnership with various companies and programs, American Heritage offers links to financial education websites for young members. We encourage parents or guardians to monitor children when they are online and to participate with children in any interactive activities offered on americanheritagecu.org American Heritage is committed to protecting the online privacy of the children who visit its website and to complying with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). COPPA prohibits unfair or deceptive acts or practices in connection with the collection, use or disclosure of personally identifiable information from and about children on the internet. 1. Personal Information – American Heritage Credit Union does not collect or use personal information of children 12 and younger through americanheritagecu.org.2. Member Contact – American Heritage Credit Union may use feedback information from readers to respond to member service requests, inquiries, comment or suggestions when initiated by the visitor to the website. 3. American Heritage may send invitations to community events and notifications of contests, scholarships or prize drawings to underage members via email and postal mail, which are sent to parent email and postal addresses on file. Email information is never sold, given or disclosed to third parties.4. Opt Out – Any member who does not wish to receive communications from American Heritage can opt out by calling 800.342.0008 and requesting to opt out. American Heritage Credit Union’s website may include links to the external websites of others. These external sites are not part of American Heritage’s services and are not under control by the credit union. Because these external websites may have privacy policies that are different than American Heritage, please consult the privacy policies of any website that asks for personally identifiable information before providing it.
